# Olga **Ulrich**

Address: Emil Oprecht Strasse 9, 8050 Zürich

**Phone:** +41 79 470 84 99

Email: olga.ulrich.ch@gmail.com

**Date of birth:** 04.05.1994

Civil status: Married, work permit B, no children



## **Profile**

I have worked 3 years in internet marketing as SEO specialist in Russia and now I want to face a new challenge here in Switzerland. Since I moved to Switzerland in 2020, I have learned German and English to a level of minimum B2. In February 2022, I completed the Fullstack Coding Camp at SIT Academy in Zurich, which I can also count among my achievements. It is extremely important for me to gain a foothold here in Switzerland, which is why I strive to integrate myself socially and professionally.

## Languages

Russian - native language German - fluent English - fluent

# Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React systems
- Phyton
- Django
- Docker
- Git Versionskontrollsystem
- SEO

Tools: MS Word, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint, Ahrefs, Google Console, Google Analytics, Screaming Frog SEO Spider, Linkresearchtools.

# Professional experience

07/2019 - 09/2020

## SEO specialist at Korus Consulting GmbH in St. Petersburg, Russia

- Accompanying SEO activities from conception to implementation.
- Support of the marketing team in search engine optimization.
- SEO monthly reports.
- Providing of SEO audits.

06/2018 - 07/2019

## SEO specialist at Topface GmbH in St. Petersburg, Russia

- Consulting and monitoring of the implementation of on-page and off-page activities concerning content, backlinks, website usability and website performance.
- SEO monthly reports.
- Providing of SEO audits.

05/2017 - 05/2018

### SEO specialist at PromoExpert GmbH in Ekaterinburg, Russia

- Management and support of clients' websites.
- SEO concept development and SEO and SEA campaign planning.
- SEO monthly reports.
- Providing of SEO audits.

### Education

09/2012 - 08/2016

State Vocational Pedagogical University, Bachelor's Degree in Pedagogy for Informatics in Ekaterinburg, Russian Federation.

09/2021 - 11/2021

German Intensive Course at Klubschule Migros in Zurich, Switzerland.

11/2021 - 02/2022

Full stack programming course at SIT Academy AG in Zurich, Switzerland.

- Working with front-end technologies: Javascript, React, Redux.
- Working with backend technologies: Python, Django, PostgreSQL.
- Deployment technologies and services: DigitalOcean, Docker.